Guide to the New York State College of Human Ecology honors theses, 1970-2017.
New York State College of Human Ecology honors theses, 1970-2018.
- Series XV. Class of 2000
  - "A Longitudinal Study on Rural Poverty and Environmental Stressors", 2000; Pranikoff, Julie West, Ilene (Box 2)
  - "Subject Specific Sensation Relationships of Natural Flavors", 2000; Mandel, Matthew (Box 2)
  - "Parental Guilt and Jealousy in the Child Care Setting: A Cross-National Study in the United States and Sweden", 2000; Sawyer, Tiffany A. (Box 5)
  - "Housing Quality and Positive Affect in Community-Dwelling Elderly", 2001; 2000; Kantrowitz, Elyse (Box 5)
- Series XVI. Class of 2001
  - Design and Environmental Analysis
    - "Effects of the Variable-Split Adjustable Keyboard on Musculoskeletal Discomfort: A Field Study", 2001; Varner, Cari Jeanne (Box 4)
    - "The Effect of VDU Font and Style on Ocular Movements During Reading", 2001; Shanis, Jenna Melissa (Box 4)
  - Division of Nutritional Sciences
    - "Predicators of Excess Weight Gain in First-Year University Students", 2001; Halbmaier, Craig A. (Box 4)
  - Human Development
    - "Family-Staff Relationships in End-of-Life Care in Nursing Homes", 2001; Goodman, Linda (Box 5)
    - "Cornell University Language Acquisition Laboratory: Analyzing Spanish Natural Speech Data of Children", 2001; Alves, Adriana (Box 5)
    - "The Transference of Visual and Auditory Source Memories in Children", 2001; Dunning, Caitlin (Box 7)
    - "The Effects of Life Events on the Division of Household Labor, Depressive Affect, Marital Satisfaction, and Marital Conflict of Older Couples", 2001; Gillan, Meghan (Box 7)
    - "Low-level Blood Lead and Intelligence in 5 year-old Children: Evidence for a Non-linear Relationship", 2001; Jusko, Todd (Box 7)
    - "College Students' Attitudes Toward the Aged and the Aging Process", 2001; Roth, Annie (Box 7)
    - "Lead Exposure and Prefrontal Functioning in Early Childhood", 2001; Santoro, Donna (Box 7)
    - "The Relation of Temperature Variance and Thermal Comfort to Learned Helplessness in Children", 2001; West, Ilene (Box 7)
    - "The Factors Affecting Female Attorneys' Rate of Promotion", 2001; Zanko, Jennifer (Box 7)
    - "The Relationship Between Body Weight and Self-Esteem in College Women", 2001; Butryn, Meghan (Box 9)
    - "Factors Associated With Individuals' Plans To Relocate For Career Growth", 2001; Yeung, Sarah Ka-wah (9)
  - Policy Analysis and Management
    - "Explaining the "Liberalness" of State Child Care Policy A Statistical Analysis", 2001; Tauber, Jill (Box 4)
    - "An Evaluation of Stakeholder Expectations in the Monroe County Juvenile Drug Court", 2001; Pawluk, Yurij Oleh (Box 4)
  - Textiles and Apparel
    - "Mass Customization of Wedding Dresses on the Internet", 2001; Choy, Rita Pui Kee (Box 4)
- Series XVII. Class of 2002
  - "An Evaluation of Richness of Representation as it Pertains to Memory Monitoring: Can Young Children Monitor?", 2002; Berry, Courtney (Box 7)
  - "Psychosocial Mentoring and Adolescent Career Development: Fostering Personal and Social Development in the Workplace", 2002; Beiswenger, Krista (Box 7)
  - "The Role of the HOME Inventory in the Relation Between Blood Lead Levels and IQ", 2002; Benas, Jessica (Box 7)
  - "Low-Level Lead Exposure and Child Behavior Problems", 2002; Conser, Jessica (Box 7)
  - "Fighting For Success: The Impact of Professors on African-American Students' Struggle for Academic Achievement in Predominantly White Universities", 2002; Davies, Carrie (Box 7)
  - "Phenomenological Exploration of Religion and Interpersonal Forgiveness", 2002; Lee, David (Box 7)
  - "Cultural Conceptions: How Cornell Students Think About Work and Family", 2002; Levin, Erica (Box 7)
  - "A Social Perspective on the Drum in Zimbabwe", 2002; Liberman, Erica (Box 7)
  - "Affect Expression and Emotion Recognition in Children", 2002; Olino, Thomas (Box 7)
  - "Contextual Environment Interactions For Cognitive Development in Toddlers: A Pathway", 2002; Rosenberg, Annie (Box 7)
  - "Cholinergic Contributions to the Enduring Effect of Early Lead Exposure on Sustained Attention and Reactivity to Errors", 2002; Srakhao, Veraanong (Box 9)
  - "The Relationship Between Bem Sex-Role Inventory and System for the Multiple Level Observation of Groups Revisited: How Well do Sex-Roles and Gender Predict Small Group Behavior?", 2002; Saufer, Suzanne (Box 9)
  - "An Examination of Spontaneous Answers to Questions About the Natural World: Do Young Children Actually Possess A 'Teleological Bias'", 2003; Ershova, Elena (Box 7)
  - "Sexual Abuse Encounters: A Risk Factor for Drug and Alcohol Abuse in Adolescent Females", 2003; Kramer, Llana (Box 8)
  - "Stress Exposure, Risk and Protective Factors, and Psychological Outcomes in Adolescents", 2003; Bufferd, Sarah (Box 8)
  - "Changes in Overt and Covert Attention, Measured via Steady-State Visual Evoked Potentials (SSVEPs)", 2003; Devine, Katy (Box 8)
  - "Individual Differences in Reasoning", 2003; Dublin, Randi (Box 8)
  - "Parenting Practices and Their Effects on the Development of African American Children", 2003; Finnegan, Michelle (Box 8)
  - "Movement Attention Coupling in Infants and Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder in Children", 2003; Friedman, Allison (Box 8)
  - "Reasoning about Explanations: How Explanations are Evaluated in Light of Disconfirming Evidence", 2003; Iwaki, Yoko (Box 8)
  - "Infants' Comprehension of Novel Words and Novel Gestures", 2003; Kakaty, Tara (Box 8)
  - "Production of Novel Words and Gestures in 8- to 22-Month Old Infants," Caryn Kerman, 2003 (Box 8)
  - "Violence as Adaptation? The Interactive Relationship between Adolescent Violence, Community Violence, and Well-Being", 2003; Latzman, Robert (Box 8)
  - "Examining the Role of Theory and Bias in Evaluating Information", 2003; Marasia, Joseph (Box 8)
  - "Religion as a Moderator of Stress and Well-Being Among Parents of Children with Autism", 2003; Rosenblum, Sara (Box 8)
  - "The Effects of Crowding and Perceived Crowding on Blood Pressure, Blood Pressure Reactivity and Recovery, and Neuroendocrine Markers: A Longitudinal Study", 2003; Shanis, Dana (Box 8)
  - "Cultural Themes in Dinnertime Conversations: A Qualitative Investigation", 2003; Sunkavalli, Kiran (Box 8)
  - "The Effects of Multiple Chronic Stressors on Cardiovascular Reactivity and Recovery In Children", 2003; Tesher, Harris (Box 8)
  - Design and Environmental Analysis
    - "A Look at the Impact of the Presence of a Community School on Neighborhood Members' Sense of a Community", 2002; Topper, Meredith (Box 4)
    - "Kitchen Design for the Elderly: Planning for Normal and Impaired Aging", 2002; Sherman, Courtney R. (Box 4)
    - "An Examination of Pilot Satisfaction with the Joint Helmet Mounted Cueing System", 2002; McElheny, Melinda Jean (Box 4)
  - Human Development
    - "Temperament and Suggestability in 3-5 Year Old Children", 2002; Lord, Heather (Box 9)
  - Policy Analysis and Management
    - "Financing Long-Term Care in the United States: The Role of Public-Private Partnerships", 2002; Nicholas, Lauren Hersch (Box 4)
    - "The Impact of Race-Related Preferences on Residential Search, Preference, and Choice", 2002; Morris, Meghan L. (Box 4)
    - "Movement Towards Market Efficiency?: An Analysis of Price Dispersion Between the Internet Market and the Ithaca Market", 2002; Steinberg, Michelle (Box 4)
  - Textiles and Apparel
    - "'Smart Systems:' Wearable Integration of Intelligent Technology", 2002; Dunne, Luch E. (Box 4)
- Series XVIII. Class of 2003
  - Design and Environmental Analysis
    - "Measurement of Children's Environmental Attitudes and Behaviors", 2003; Stecker, Rachel (Box 5)
    - "The Usability Comparison of Two Touch Screen Point-of Sale (POS) System Platforms in Family Dining Restaurants", 2003; Levitt, Mariah (Box 5)
    - "Restorative Elements in Child Care Facilities: Effects on Behavior and Development in Preschool Children", 2003; Hegarty, Caroline (Box 5)
  - Division of Nutritional Sciences
    - "An Analysis of Song and Female Choice: Avian Brain Regions in Relation to Evolutionary Selection Factors", 2003; Weng Debbie (Box 4)
  - Policy Analysis and Management
    - "Information Technology's New Role in the Healthcare Industry", 2003; Gleicher, Lora (Box 4)
    - "Profiling the Demand for Student Leadership Training Within the College of Human Ecology", 2003; Levy, Daniel Blake (Box 4)
    - "An Analysis of the Cable Industry from 1996 to 2001", 2003; Reichenberg, David (Box 4)
    - "The Effects of School Racial Composition on Academic Achievement in Adolescence", 2003; Lee, Hedwig Eugenie (Box 4)
    - "Courage and Despair in the Face of La Crisis: Middle-Class Argentines Tell Their Stories," (Cornell Presidential Research Scholars Senior Project), 2003; Lerner, Karen (Box 9)
- Series XIX. Class of 2004
  - "Discrepant Perceptions of Parental Responsiveness in Mother-Adolescent Dyads and Psychological Distress in Adolescents", 2004; Callahan, Corissa Lynn (Box 8)
  - "The Effects of Gender and Motivation on Causal Reasoning", 2004; Howell, Kathryn (Box 8)
  - "Hospicare:An Assessment of Bereavement Services", 2004; Kwartner, Jason (Box 8)
  - "The Motivation to Disconfirm Can Be a Double-edged Sword", 2004; Liang, Victoria (Box 8)
  - "Elder Abuse: An Assessment of Mandatory Reporting Laws", 2004; Lipitz, Stacey Jennifer (Box 8)
  - "The Effect of the Mother-Child Relationship, Family Form, and Maternal Presence on Adolescent Drug Use in African American Families", 2004; Meyers, Noah M. (Box 8)
  - "Religious Conceptualization and Coping Strategies in College Students", 2004; Notheis, Kimberley Ann (Box 8)
  - "Gender, Extraversion, Life Events, and Depression", 2004; Richards, Jessica (Box 8)
  - "Some Anomalies are More Problematic than Others", 2004; Slator, Lindsay B. (Box 8)
  - "Personality Differences in Eyewitness Identification", 2004; Totino, Maryann (Box 8)
  - "Do Social Networks Provide a Buffer for the Effect of Stress on Psychological Distress? An Investigation of the Influence of Rural Mothers' Social Networks", 2004; Ziwich, Rachel Theresa (Box 8)
  - "An Experience Sampling Study of Stress and Coping Among Low and Middle-Income Youth", 2004; Simon, Nicole S. (Box 9)
  - Design and Environmental Analysis
    - "The Effects of Increased Technology Complexity and Reduced Staff Shift-Work on Visual and Mental Performance", 2004; Thurston, Stephanie A. (Box 5)
  - Human Development
    - "The Effectiveness of Second Step, A Violence Prevention Curriculum, In The Ithaca, New York Area", 2004 (Box 9)
    - "Arts Integration and Classroom Management Styles in the Binghamton City School District Elementary Schools", 2004; Wechsler, Rachel (Box 9)
  - Policy Analysis and Management
    - "Making the Grade: A Longitudinal Analysis of Education and Adult Obesity", 2004; Cook, Allison (Box 4)
    - "Women in Community Organizing: A Mixed Method Study of Women Leaders from the Northwest Bronx Community and Clergy Coalition", 2004; Vu, Ha My (Box 4)
    - "From Rx to OTC: An Analysis of the Changes in Flow, Format, and Content of Print Advertisements in the Smoking Cessation Pharmaceutical Industry", 2004; Crocco, Michelle M. (Box 4)
    - "Substitutability of Prescription Drug Benefits for Hospitalization and Emergency Room Visits", 2004; Chu, Robert A. (Box 4)
    - "The Establishment and Evolution of State-Mandated Testing", 2004; Rathod, Anar K. (Box 4)
- Series XX. Class of 2005
  - Design and Environmental Analysis
    - "Community Resources and Adolescent Planning Styles", 2005; Davidoff, Kate (Box 5)
  - Division of Nutritional Sciences
    - "Nutrition Knowledge of Cornell University Students: Nutrition knowledge, attitudes, and behaviors of nutrition and non-nutrition majors at Cornell University", 2005; Furst, Jessica Rachel (Box 4)
    - "Functional Characterization of a-Tocopherol Transfer Protein Ataxia with Vitamin E Deficient Mutants", 2005; Bernardo, Katrina (Box 10)
  - Policy Analysis and Management
    - "The Effect of the State of Israel's Education System on Peace Process Perceptions by Israeli Youth", 2005; Stern, Ari Nathan (Box 4)
    - "Explanations for the Link Between Body Weight and Labor Market Outcomes", 2005; Ziskroit, Harris Ian (Box 4)
    - "Diversity of Extracurricular Activities", 2005; Frongillo, Dominic E. (Box 4)
    - "Does Market Capital Translate into Marital Capital?: A Comparison of Marital Homogamy Between Professional and Non-Professional Women Upon Remarriage", 2005; Sharma, Parijat (Box 4)
    - "The Effects of a Threat Level Change by the Department of Homeland Security on U.S. Airline and Defense Stocks", 2005; Pandolfini, Michael (Box 9)
    - "Child Protective Services Use of Precautionary Measures Against False Allegations", 2005; Lipitz, Allison Nicole (Box 9)
  - Textiles and Apparel
    - "Understanding the Race/Class Gap in Academic Achievement", 2005; Elliot, Sarah (Box 4)
  - Human Development
    - "Maltreatment and Anti-Social Behavior: Understanding the Pathways of Resilience", 2005; Siegel, Alana (Box 9)
- Series XXI. Class of 2006
  - Design and Environmental Analysis
    - "Volumetric Deformation: A New Objective Measure to Study Chair Comfort Using 3D Body Scanning Technology", Agarwal, Anshu; Online
  - Division of Nutritional Sciences
    - "Effects of Male Aggressive Behavior on Female Mate Choice in Japanese Quail, Coturnix Japonica", 2006; Riccardi, Elizabeth; CD#303
    - "Escaping Food Insecurity: A Portrait of Several Rural New York Families Using Mixed-Methods Analysis", 2006; Lent, Megan (Box 9)
  - Human Development
    - "Individual Differences in the Development of Effortful Control in Preschoolers", 2006; Muenke, Hanna; CD#302
    - "The Mediating Role of Preschool Play Behavior in the Relationship Between Poverty and First Grade Socioemotional Competence", 2006; Rosenbaum, Jennifer L.; CD#304
    - "Sub-clinical Obsessive Compulsive Disorder and its Relation to Academic Achievement and Defensive Pessimism", 2006; Celano, Mark; CD#305
    - "The Quality of Memory for Events that Alter Identity", 2006; Katz, Judith; CD#306
    - "The Development of Executive Control: Behavioral and Neutral Activity in a Proposed Pediatric Stroop Task", 2006; LaVallee, Sarah (Box 9)
  - Textiles and Apparel
    - "Fashioning the Tourist: An Andean Travelers Wardrobe - A Study in Curatorial Practice", 2006; Staiti, Alana (Box 10)
- Series XXII. Class of 2007
  - "Health and the Persistence of Food Insecurity in Rural New York Families", 2007; Petrovic, Lindsay Elizabeth (Box 9)
  - "Community Violence, Child Maltreatment, and Children's Behavioral Problems: An Ecological Perspective", 2007; Wong, Nina (Box 10)
- Series XXIII. Class of 2008
  - Human Development
    - "Meta-conceptual Thinking and Positive Outcomes Among Youth in a Refuge Camp", 2008; Ojalehto, Bethany (Box 9)
    - "It's Always Good to Think About Yourself: Self-Evaluations of Performance are Associated with Higher Self-Esteem", 2008; Poliskin, Dara (Box 9)
  - Division of Nutritional Sciences
    - "Sleeping, Eating and Time Use", 2008; Nulty, Matthew Robert (Box 10)
- Series XXIV. Class of 2012
  - Human Development
    - "You Can't Handle the Truth: Gist Memory Leads to Predictable False Memory Effects with Age", 2012; Cohen, Brittany (Box 9)
    - "Turn to Learn: How Spatial Experience and Left-Right Language Matter in Spatial Cognition", 2012; Dinowitz, Abbie (Box 9)
    - "Barriers to Birth Control Use in College Women", 2012; Gichane, Margaret (Box 9)
  - Textiles and Apparel
    - "Ithaca Underground: How Dress is Used to Show Community", 2012; Sutton, Audrey (Box 10)
- Series XXV. Class of 2013
  - Human Development
    - "Be Afraid, Be Very Afraid: Predictive Effects of Fearful and Fatalistic Attitudes on Young Adult Risk Behavior", 2013; Avrutine, Julie (Box 10)
    - "Does Parenting Matter? Exploring the Link Among Poverty, Mental State Language, and Executive Function in Infancy", 2013; Camerota, Marie (Box 10)
    - "Examining Parental Role in Children's Concepts of Choice", 2013; Distenfeld, Shelby (Box 10)
    - "The Effect of Poverty on Maternal Responsiveness, Child Negative Affect, and Effortful Control", 2013; Diu, Maggie (Box 10)
    - "Willingness to Grant Accommodations to Individuals Labeled as Mentally Ill and Physically Ill", 2013; Finn, Natalie (Box 10)
    - "Integrating the Mind and Body: Uncovering the Relationship between Attention and Body Movement in Infants", 2013; Menon, Meera (Box 10)
    - "An Investigation of Perceived Family Warmth, Non-Suicidal Self-Injury (NSSI), and NSSI Recovery", 2013; Morgan, Rebecca A. (Box 10)
    - "Greater Connectivity is Associated with Greater Framing Bias: A Combined DTI and MRI Study", 2013; Nollet, Zachary (Box 10)
    - "Comparing the Diagnostic Validity of ASPD Preceded by Conduct Disorder with Adult-Only Antisocial Personality Disorder", 2013; Tusa, Brittany (Box 10)
  - Textiles and Apparel
    - "The Origin and Evolution of "Prep" and its Socioeconomic Relevance", 2013; Lingala, Anu (Box 10)
- Series XXVI. Class of 2014
  - Human Development
    - "Relationships Between Domestic Violence, Social Support, and Maternal Psychosocial and Behavioral Outcomes", 2014; Atzl, Victoria (Box 10)
    - "Linking Emotional Competence and Learning Spanish as a Second Language", 2014; Azar, Martina (Box 10)
    - "Impact of Trauma Exposure on Gray Matter Volume: Assessing the Role of Development", 2014; DuPre, Elizabeth (Box 10)
    - "Gender Congruity and Physical Attractiveness in Leadership Evaluation", 2014; Fok, Evelyn (Box 10)
    - "Young Children Use Statistical Sampling to Infer Their Own Preferences", 2014; Gentilini, Lara (Box 10)
    - "Developmental Differences in Spatial Transformation Ability During Infancy", 2013; Marfurt, Samantha (Box 10)
    - "An Examination of System-and Individual-Level Factors Which May Be Associated with the Urban- Rural Disparity in Hospice Utilization", 2014; McDarby, Meghan (Box 10)
- Series XXVII. Class of 2015
  - Human Development
    - "Developmental Differences in Spatial Categorization of Korean Infants", 2015; Ahn, Yeo Jin (Box 10)
    - "Influence of Aging on the Neural Correlates of Autobiographical Memory, Prospection, and Theory of Mind", 2015; Brite, Chelsea (Box 10)
    - "The Intergroup Dialogue Project's Impact on Student Attitudes and Behaviors Regarding Diversity and Inclusion", 2015; Fletcher, Katelyn (Box 10)
    - "Assessing Impulsivity and Risk in Emerging Adulthood", 2015; Katz, Zoe Amelia (Box 10)
    - "Home is Where We Are Together: Reunion Sex Assists the Restoration of Physiological Co-Regulation in Romantic Couples", 2015; Massaro, Devin (Box 10)
    - "Only Skin-Deep: Revising First Impressions of Faces", 2015; Meagher, Brian (Box 10)
    - "The Effect of Minimal Group Bias in Memory and Attitude Over Time", 2015; Monks, Grace (Box 10)
  - Fiber Science and Apparel Design
    - "Increased Conductivity of Electrospun Pedot:PSS Nanofibers and Core-Shell Pedot Microfibers", 2015; Levitt, Ariana (Box 10)
- Series XXVIII. Class of 2016
  - Human Development
    - "Critical Thinking and Decision-making in Modern Day Physicians", 2016; Dunlea, James Patrick (Box 10)
    - "Race and Conceptions of Intelligence: Exploring how College Students of Different Races may Differ in Their Ideas of Intelligence", 2016; Francis, Trenel (Box 10)
    - "Reflections as a Resource: Mitigating the Effects of Gender Macroaggressions", 2016; Inniss-Thompson, Misha (Box 10)
    - "The Neural Correlates of Language Processing: A Meta Analysis of AD and MCI Studies", 2016; Janmohamed, Azraa (Box 10)
    - "The Time Course of False Memory Processes", 2016; Lee, Wei-Feng Aaron (Box 10)
    - "Expected Outcomes of Co-Rumination in Emerging Adults", 2016; McCormick, Kathleen (Box 10)
    - "Evaluating the Maturational Disparity Hypothesis: Is there a Physical and Cognitive Mismatch in Early Maturing Girls", 2016; McGuire, Taylor (Box 10)
    - "The Effect of the Color Red on Sexual Attraction: Replication and Extension in People with Same-Sex Attraction", 2016; Terenzi, Paisley (Box 10)
- Series XXIX. Class of 2017
  - Human Development
    - "Localization of Oxytocin-Like Containing Neurons in the Highly Vocal Gulf Toadfish with Comparisons to Mammals", 2017; Fernandez, Anna Claire (Box 10)
    - "When was Your Earliest Memory and How Do You Remember More Accurately? Young Adults Postdating Early Childhood Memories", 2017; Khuu, Angel (Box 10)
    - "Individual Differences in Perspective Taking with Interactive Social Learning", 2017; LaGrant, Brian (Box 10)
    - "The Effect of Minimal Group Membership on Children's Susceptibility to Suggestive Questioning", 2017; Sharpstene, Leona Marie (Box 10)
    - "Racial and Ethnic Differences in Pain Self-Management Techniques Among Older Adults with Chronic Pain", 2017; Sidhu, Sharendra (Box 10)
    - "Intrinsic Functional Connectivity of the Default Mode Network is Associated with Individual Differences in Social Cognition", 2017; Tsai, Hsiang; Lockrow, Amber; Spreng, Nathan R. (Box 10)
    - "The Role of Autonomic Processes in Adaptive Memory", 2017; Winebrake, Deaven (Box 10)
  - Design and Environmental Analysis
    - "Designing Undesigned Interior Playscapes:Implications from Junk Playgrounds and Makerspaces", 2017; Lee, Sohyun (Box 10)
- Series XXX. Class of 2018
  - Human Development
    - "Dehumanizing Consequences of Observing Social Exclusion", 2018; Avila, Matthew (Box 10)
    - "Family Estrangement and its Effects on College Students", 2018; Chen, Gregory (Box 10)
    - "Tentative Testing: Applying Fuzzy-trace Theory to Sexually Transmitted Infections (STI) Testing Decisions in Adolescents and Young Adults", 2018; Chen, Stacey (Box 10)
    - "Memories Reimagined: Quantum Entanglement in Human Memory Activation", 2018; Chen, Xi Richard (Box 10)
    - "Caregiver Interactions During Playtime with Their Children", 2018; Guzman, Tati (Box 10)
    - "The Context of Race in the Perceptual-Response to Fear and Anger", 2018; Hill, Alize (Box 10)
    - "Assessing the Cognitive Impacts of an Impaired Attentional Filter in Older Adults", 2018; Jegarl, Anita (Box 10)
    - "Time Perception and Pain", 2018; Kruse, Jessica (Box 10)
    - "Rejection Thoughts and Relationship Outcomes: Exploring Rejection Sensistity in Girls' Relationships", 2018; Lesnick, Julia (Box 10)
    - "Development and Validation of the Dietarian Identity Questionnaire: Assesing Self-Perceptions of Animal-Product Consumption", 2018; Rosenfeld, Daniel (Box 10)
    - "Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder and Identity: Diagnostic Correlates, Contextual Malleability and Domain Specificity", 2018; Rosenthal, Emily (Box 10)
    - "Parents, Play, and Spatial Perception: The Relationship Between Parental Scaffolding During Play and Infants' Mental Rotation Abilities", 2018; Sheridan, Laura (Box 10)
    - "Cumulative Risk in Childhood Ecological Systems and Severity of Hyperactivity/Impulsivity", 2018; Sloan, Greta Ives (Box 10)
    - "Examining the Influence of Emotion on the Illusory Correlation Effect", 2018; Stansell, Alexandria (Box 10)